Information Studies, Department of; Records ua671
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Course Materials, 1927-1992; 2; 6.2 cubic ft.
  - LIB 666 Censorship: Preventive Strategies and Policies - Farley, Halsey, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - LIB 666 Computer Based Bibliographic Searching - Burgess, Gavryck, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - LIB 666 Evaluation of Library Services - Martin, 1986; Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - LIB 666 Federal and State Sources of Legal Information, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - LIB 666 History of Libraries and Librarianships - Clarkin, 1980-1981; Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - LIB 666 Indexing and Abstracting - Stevens, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - LIB 666 Individual Reader in and Information Age - Mitchell, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - LIB 666 Information Environment and Public Information Policy - Stevenson, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - LIB 666 Information Resources Management for Government/ Public Sector Decision Making - Pavlson, 1982-1983; Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - LIB 666 Legal Bibliography - Morehead, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - LIB 666 Library Instruction for Librarians - Roberts, 1979-1981; Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - LIB 666 Library Media Skills Curriculum - Halsey, 1980; 1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - LIB 666 Making Connections - Halsey, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - LIB 666 Media Selection - Katz, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - LIB 666 Micro-based Computer Assisted Instruction - Burgess, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - LIB 666 Microcomputer-Based Text Management and Full-Text Retrieval Systems - Hoyle, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - LIB 666 National Information Policy - Klempner, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - LIB 666 Planning Library and Media Center Services, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - LIB 666 Records Management - Whalen, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - LIB 666 Reference Update - Halsey, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - LIB 666 Software Packages Evaluation/Selection - Saffady, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - LIB 666 State and Local Government Sources - Morehead, 1978; 1985 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - LIB 666 State, Local, and International Publications - Morehead, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - LIB 666 Studies in Descriptive Cataloging, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - LIB 666 Technology and Nonprint Resource for Libraries - Halsey, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - LIB 668 Internship - Mitchell, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - LIB 668 Internship - Vaillancourt, Whalen, 1982-1983; 1985 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - LIB 669 Independent - Study, 1975; Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - LIB 672 Library Materials for Children - Orsini, 1981; Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - LIB 673 History of Children's Literature - Mitchell, Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - LIB 674 Library Services to Children - Mitchell, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - LIB 674 Library Services to Children - Orsini, 1971; 1974; 1978-1979; 1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - LIB 675 Curriculum and Supportive Resources - Aceto, 1981-1983; Undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - LIB 675 Curriculum and Supportive Resources - Halsey, Orsini, Lownes, 1977-1978; 1984 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - LIB 675 Curriculum and Supportive Resources - Lenz, 1989; 1991 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - LIB 676 Administration of School Media Centers - Farley, 1976-1979; 1982-1983; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - LIB 676 Administration of School Media Centers - Nelson, 1981; Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - LIB 676 Problems in Administration and Supervision of School System Libraries - Smith, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - LIB 680 Cataloging and Cataloging Codes - Stevenson, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - LIB 680 Content Analysis - Aceto, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - LIB 680 Film Literature - Aceto, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - LIB 680 History of Printing and Publishing - Clarkin, 1976; 1980; Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - LIB 680 Indexing Vocabularies - Hoyle, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - LIB 680 Information Processing - Hoyle, 1982-1983; 1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - LIB 680 Information Sources and Services - Vaillancourt, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - LIB 680 Library Catalogs - Hoyle, 1978; 1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - LIB 680 Multitype Library Cooperatives and Networks-Halsey, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - LIB 680 Music of Young Adults - Stevenson, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - LIB 680 Neglected Clienteles - Morehead, 1975; 1984; 1986; 1988-1989; 1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - LIB 680 Neglected Clienteles - Morehead, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - LIB 680 Reference Books for the Twenty-First Century - Halsey, 1977; 1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - LIB 680 Research Studies in School Librarianship, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - LIB 680 Resource Sharing - Hoyle, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - LIB 680 School Library Media Centers for the Year 2000 - Aceto, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - LIB 680 Secondary Information - Lipetz, 1981-1983; 1989; Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - LIB 680 Seminar - Aceto, 1973-1974; 1978-1979; 1990; Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - LIB 680 Seminar on Archives - Whalen, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - LIB 680 Sexism in Children's Bookz - Orsini, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - LIB 680 Small Press and Little Magazines - Hoyle, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - LIB 680 State and Local Documents - Morehead, 1973; 1987; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - LIB 680 State Library Problems - Whalen, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - LIB 699 Master's Thesis in Library Science, 1972-1973; 1975; Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - LIB 701 Proseminar ( 6th Year Program) - Lipetz, Martin, 1978-1980; 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Professional Organizations and Associations, 1916-1990; 3; 3.3 cubic ft.
  This series contains correspondence and information provided to and from the various national, regional, state, and local organizations and associations in which the Department of Information Studies was involved as well as records pertaining to committees and other groups involved with the State University of New York (SUNY) in general. Of particular note is the large amount of records to and from the American Library Association (ALA), a professional organization whose function, among others, is the accreditation of all the information science and library schools in the nation.
  - Adult Education Council, 1944; 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ALA - Accreditation, 1951; 1957; 1960-1961; 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ALA - Accreditation, 1965-1966; 1972-1973; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ALA - Accreditation, 1974-1975; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ALA - Accreditation, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ALA - Accreditation Award, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ALA - Accreditation Manual and Standards, 1971-1972; 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ALA - Accreditation Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ALA - Accreditation Self-Study Report Draft ( 1 of 2), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ALA - Accreditation Self-Study Report Draft ( 2 of 2), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ALA - Accreditation Self-Study Report Complete ( 1 of 2), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ALA - Accreditation Self-Study Report Complete ( 2 of 2), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - ALA - Accreditation Self-Study Report ( 1 of 2), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - ALA - Accreditation Self-Study Report ( 2 of 2), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - ALA - Accrediting Team Visit, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ALA - Board of Education for Librarianship - Accreditation ( 1 of 4), 1926-1932; 1935-1936; 1940; 1948; 1950-1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - ALA - Board of Education for Librarianship - Accreditation ( 2 of 4), 1926-1932; 1935-1936; 1940; 1948; 1950-1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ALA - Board of Education for Librarianship - Accreditation ( 3 of 4), 1926-1932; 1935-1936; 1940; 1948; 1950-1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - ALA - Board of Education for Librarianship - Accreditation ( 4 of 4), 1926-1932; 1935-1936; 1940; 1948; 1950-1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ALA - Board of Education for Librarianship - Correspondence, 1928-1929; 1943-1946; 1949-1952 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - ALA - Board of Education for Librarianship - Enrollment Statistics ( 1 of 3), 1929-1953; 1955; 1957 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - ALA - Board of Education for Librarianship - Enrollment Statistics ( 2 of 3), 1929-1953; 1955; 1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ALA - Board of Education for Librarianship - Enrollment Statistics ( 3 of 3), 1929-1953; 1955; 1957 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - ALA - Board of Education for Librarianship - Statements and Reviews, 1937; 1945; 1949; 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ALA - Committee on Accreditation- Accreditation Report, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ALA - Committee on Accreditation Annual Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - ALA - Committee on Accreditation Annual Reports, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - ALA - Committee on Accreditation Annual Reports, 1978-1981; 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - ALA - Committee on Accreditation Course Outlines and Syllabi, 1982-1983; 1988-1990; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ALA - Committee on Accreditation - Review of School of Library and Information Science Annual Report, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ALA - Committee on Accreditation - Statement of Interpretation, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - ALA - Committee on Measurement and Guidance, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ALA - Conference on the Bibliographic Control of Library Literature ( 1 of 3), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - ALA - Conference on the Bibliographic Control of Library Literature ( 2 of 3), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - ALA - Conference on the Bibliographic Control of Library Literature ( 3 of 3), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - ALA - Correspondence - General, 1931; 1933; 1935; 1937; 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - ALA - Correspondence - General, 1941; 1948-1950; 1952-1955; 1957; 1965 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ALA - Financial Assistance Reports, 1969; 1978-1980; 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ALA - Library Education Division, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ALA - Library Congress Inquiry Team - Racial Discrimination Report, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - ALA - Publications, 1980-1984; 1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - ALA - Racial/ Ethnic Reports, 1962; 1972; 1978-1979; 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - ALA - Standards for Accreditation, 1951; 1958-1959; 1962; 1972; 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ALA - Standards for Accreditation, 1977; 1979-1981; Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - American Association of State Libraries, 1961-1963; Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - American Association of University Professors (A.A.V.P), 1965; Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - American Council on Education, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - American Society for Information Science (ASIS), 1969; 1971; 1978-1979; 1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - American Society for Information Science (ASIS)- Membership, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - American Society for Information Science/ Special Libraries Association- Student Chapter Newsletter, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Association of American Library School, 1934; 1938-1948; 1950-1957; Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Association of Law Libraries of Upstate New York (ALLUNY), 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Association of Library and Information Science Education ( 1 of 3), 1964-1966; 1969; 1971-1973; 1979-1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Association of Library and Information Science Education ( 2 of 3), 1964-1966; 1969; 1971-1973; 1979-1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Association of Library and Information Science Education ( 3 of 3), 1964-1966; 1969; 1971-1973; 1979-1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Association of Records Managers and Administrators- Survey, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Chicago University Graduate Library School, 1936; 1948; 1951-1952; 1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Citzens' Library Council of New York State, 1982-1985; Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Columbia University - School of Library Science, 1932; 1939; 1942-1943; 1946-1947; 1951-1954 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Columbia University - School of Library Science, 1962; 1964-1965; Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Department of Civil Service, 1951-1952; 1962 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - ERIC, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Geneseo State University Teachers College, 1926; 1932-1934; 1944; 1952-1954; 1963 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Grolier Society, 1951-1953; Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Hudson Mohawk Library, 1945; 1955; 1965; Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Kansas State Teachers College, 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Knapp School Libraries Project, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Law Library Association of Greater New York, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Library School Student Association, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Library Schools - Blank Application Forms, Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Library Schools - Blank Application Forms, Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 5)
  - Library Schools - General, 1953-1954; 1962; 1964 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Library Student Association of Albany (LSAA) - Newsletter, ca. 1970 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Library Trustees Foundation of New York State, 1952; 1960-1962; 1965-1966; Undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Medical Library Association, 1969-1971; 1973; 1983 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Melvil Dui Chowder and Marching Association, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Middle States Association, 1952; 1955; 1960-1962; 1970-1971; Undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Mid-Hudson Library Association, 1964; 1978 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - National Library of Medicine, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - NDEA, 1962; 1965; 1967 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - New England Library Association, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - New York Library Association (NYLA), 1944-1948; 1950-1953; 1957; 1959 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - New York Library Association (NYLA), 1962; 1964-1968; 1970; 1972; 1974 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - New York Library Association (NYLA), 1975-1976; 1978; 1980-1986; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - New York Library Association (NYLA) - Conference (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - New York Library Association (NYLA) - Conference (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - New York State College for Teachers - Annual Round Table - Library Section, 1932-1935 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - New York State College for Teachers - Audio-Visual Department, 1948-1949; 1953-1954; 1956-1957; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - New York State College for Teachers - Budget Advisory Committee, 1949-1951; 1957-1959 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - New York State College for Teachers - Committee for the Improvement of College Teaching, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - New York State College for Teachers - Committee on General Education, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - New York State College for Teachers - Committee on Space and Schedule (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - New York State College for Teachers - Curriculum and Graduate Committee, 1950-1954; Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - New York State Interagency Information Group (NYSIIG) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - New York State Law Library (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - New York State Library, 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - New York State Library, 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - New York State Library Schools - Meetings, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - New York State School Libraries, 1928-1929; 1939-1941 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Regents, 1960-1962; Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Research Foundation, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Schenectady County Public Library (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Schenectady Public Schools, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Senate Professional Organization (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Soroptimist International of Albany - Program (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Southeastern New York Library Resources Council, Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Special Libraries Association (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Student Clubs, 1937-1942; Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - SUNY - Academic Policy Committee (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - SUNY - Administrative Committee, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - SUNY - ALA - Student Chapter (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - SUNY - Alumni Association - Annual Lecture (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - SUNY - Alumni Association - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - SUNY - Alumni Association - List of Alumni, 1916-1951 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - SUNY - Alumni Association - Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - SUNY - Budget Advisory Committee (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - SUNY - Cabinet, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - SUNY - Capital Area School Development Association (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - SUNY - Capital Area School Development Association (CASDA), 1962-1963; Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - SUNY - Center for Inter-American Studies, 1961-1965; Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - SUNY - Committee on Academic Standing, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - SUNY - Committee on Communication, 1969-1971; Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - SUNY - Committee on Continuing Education, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - SUNY - Committee on Institutional Funds, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - SUNY - Committee on Institutional Funds, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - SUNY - Deans' Conference - Correspondence, 1971-1973; 1975-1977; Undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - SUNY - Deans/Directors Retreat (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - SUNY - Deans' Meetings, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - SUNY - Educational Policies Council, 1971-1973; Undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - SUNY - Educational Policies Council, 1971-1973; Undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - SUNY - Faculty Council, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - SUNY - Faculty Senate, 1974-1980; Undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - SUNY - Faculty Senate, 1974-1980; Undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - SUNY - Graduate Academic Council, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - SUNY - Graduate Academic Council, 1968-1972; 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - SUNY - Graduate Academic Council, 1976-1983 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - SUNY - Institutional Research Committee (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - SUNY - Library School Admissions Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - SUNY - Library School Alumni Association, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - SUNY - Library School Personnel Committee, ca. 1967; 1970-1972; Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - SUNY - Promotion Board, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - SUNY - University Fund, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - SUNY - University Library, 1965-1970; 1978-1979; Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - SUNY - University Senate, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Syracuse University (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Technical Institutes, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - University of Illinois, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Upper Hudson Library (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Book Exchange (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Office of Education, 1965-1968; Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Who's Who in Library Service (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Former Faculty Personnel Files, 1956-2004; 4; 1.17 cubic ft.
  RESTRICTED. Contains personally identifiable information. Consult an archivist for details.
  This series contains the personnel files of a number of former faculty members in the Department of Information Science. This series contains transcripts, applications for employment, correspondence with the various deans and chairs, material related to tenure review and promotions, student evaluations, newspaper clippings and news reports, photographs, retirement documents, and the curriculum vitae of the faculty. Because of the large amount of private information included, this series has been restricted.
  - Bertot, John, 1997-2000; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Branch, Jennifer, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Galvin, Thomas, 1989-1995; 1999-2000; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Galvin, Thomas, 1989-1995; 1999-2000; Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 6)
  - Halsey, Richard, 1968-1969; 1971-1977; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Halsey, Richard, 1968-1969; 1971-1977; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Halsey, Richard, 1978-1982; 1984-1987; 1989-1991; 1994-1998; Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Halsey, Richard, 1978-1982; 1984-1987; 1989-1991; 1994-1998; Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 7)
  - Katz, William, 1966-1975; 1978-1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Katz, William, 1966-1975; 1978-1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Katz, William, 1966-1975; 1978-1999; Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 8)
  - Kingma, Bruce, 1994-2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Kingma, Bruce, 1994-2000 (Oversized 12, Folder 9)
  - Klempner, Irving, 1967-1976; 1978-1982; 1984-1991; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Klempner, Irving, 1967-1976; 1978-1982; 1984-1991; Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 10)
  - Lenz, Millicent, 1985-1986; 1988-1995; 1998-2004; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lenz, Millicent, 1985-1986; 1988-1995; 1998-2004; Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 11)
  - Lipetz, Ben-Ami, 1962-1963; 1965-1966; 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lipetz, Ben-Ami, 1980-1995; 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Lipetz, Ben-Ami, 1980-1995; 1997-1999 (Oversized 12, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell, David, 1961-1966; 1968-1972; 1975-1976; 1978-1991; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mitchell, David, 1961-1966; 1968-1972; 1975-1976; 1978-1991; Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 13)
  - Morehead, Joseph, 1969-1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Morehead, Joseph, 1969-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Morehead, Joseph, 1981-1982; 1984-1989; 1991-1996; 1998-2003; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Morehead, Joseph, 1981-1982; 1984-1989; 1991-1996; 1998-2003; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Morehead, Joseph, 1981-1982; 1984-1989; 1991-1996; 1998-2003; Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 14)
  - Saffady, William, 1970-1971; 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Saffady, William, 1970-1971; 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Saffady, William, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Saffady, William, 1990-1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Saffady, William, 1987-1990 (Oversized 12, Folder 15)
  - Walker, Geraldine, 1979-1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Walker, Geraldine, 1990-1991; 1993-1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Walker, Geraldine, 1979-1989; 1990-1991; 1993-1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 16)
- Subject Files, 1923-1979; 5; 0.9 cubic ft.
  This series contains records that do not fit into the other series, this includes a scrapbook, biographical histories of the department as well as certain members of the faculty, and accession and circulation records from the now defunct Hawley Library.
  - Accessions 1-3600, 1926-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accessions 3601-8000, 1926-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Accessions 8000-, 1926-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Albany Municipal Documents: A Directory of Services (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Albany, New York: A Guide to Selected Local Records (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bibliography of the History of Albany, New York (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Capital District Information Sources (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Circulation Record Book, 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Circulation Record Book, 1939-1943 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Centralized Processing Institute, 1956-1958; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Conferences - General, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Exhibits (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Library Journal, 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Library School Scrapbook - Bruins, Ella, 1926-1936 (Oversized 11, Item 1)
  - Library Service Now: In New York State (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - New York State Library School: From Columbia to Albany to Columbia (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Pritchard, Martha C. - Biographical Materials, 1929-1930 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Redoubt (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Rockefeller College - 70th Anniversary of Husted, Draper, and Hawley Halls (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Social and Political Aspects of Librarianship (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - "World of Books" Television Script (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - History of the Department of Librarianship, 1925-1935; 1951-1953; Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Information Studies - 50th Anniversary (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Libraries of Teacher-Training Institutions, 1951-1952; Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Library Instruction Materials, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Web Archives, 2011 February 2-2016 September 18; 6; 313 captures
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service. This page includes links to both the university's collection and the Internet Archive's public collection.